babysavers.com 2013-09-13

# Privacy Policy - BabySavers

Your privacy is very, very important to me!

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.babygoodbuys.com. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to www.babygoodbuys.com users based on their visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Other third-party advertising companies may be used to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).  Baby GoodBuys has no access to or control over the information that may be collected via these cookies

**Collection of Personal Information**

When visiting Baby GoodBuys, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is only used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Other Ad Network Privacy Information**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please  see <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Links to Third Party Websites**

There are thousands of links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions, please [contact me](http://www.babysavers.com/contact).
